I'm going to introduce you to the platform
Pragma Internal Surveys, which I had
opportunity to develop, during my
permanent contract at Soft Concept for almost a year
and a half. The platform is intended to
administer a survey and access the
results as soon as it closes. There are 2
profiles on the platform: the administrator
profile (Pragma) and the head of survey
profile. The manager
will be asking for his
employees either by email or by
mail with 1 QR code. If I
connect like Pragma. Pragma will
have a list of companies or
services with the manager
login, email and when it
was notified of the creation of the account.
We can change the information,
delete, create an account at any time,
download the user guide
of the platform,
have a FAQ
e.g. for survey objectives
internal, what the platform offers,
how do we analyze the results, how
they are introduced. So, here the
proposed questionnaires on the
platform. Interpersonal skills,
quality of meetings, operation
team, transformation project,
safety at work. It is possible
also to make a custom
questionnaire to really probe the
employees on topics that will
matter to the organization, the company
which will use the platform.
Pragma will also have a follow-up, so
the number of investigations that have been carried out
customer-side and date
of the last survey. We're going to have too
a consolidated report.
We will choose 2 dates on a survey to be
consolidate (e.g. quality of
meetings). We will
select the survey leaders
so for example all companies
on this investigation there and the dates.
There you go, the report is going
to be generated. If I hadn't selected
enough
respondents, I would not have had the
ability to generate the report. In
fact, there is a notion of
confidentiality, if a report has less than
10 respondents, it will not be generated.
So, here, we are in a platform of
demonstration, so the quota has been limited
to one for test concerns, but in
production it is well of 10. So there
we have a report, for example, on the investigation
on the quality of the meetings here, so 4
surveys, 11 respondents. There this
what we are going to do is that now we
go create an account. We create an account
Mail of head of survey. So I'm going to
put a temporary address.
Phone number, no. So, the
logo and the signature. In fact, we're going to
be able to customize surveys with
the logo, so by default, is the logo
and the signing of Pragma which will be
used. So I'm going to let
Pragma's signature. I'm going to
put for example this.  Finally, there is the
notion of consent, I can accept
or not that my company's data
can be aggregated to establish
overall results. I validate. I have
well received the email, I will be able to
set my password with
minimum 8 characters for the sake of
security.
My account has been successfully created. I can
click here to go directly to the
platform. So now I'm redirected to
the login page from earlier.
I'll be able to launch my first survey
so for that I will have to
set my settings. There, I find
the logo I had defined earlier.
Here is the color of the questionnaire,
Pragma's signature, the categories
So, for example
we can decide not to
define categories, 1 category,
2 categories or 3 categories for example
for sites, knowing that it is necessary when
even respecting the quota of 10 people.
So we can, for example,
select a category, for example, the
city and we will select for example
Paris, Lyon. Therefore,
we can validate here,
The settings have been saved.
There I will be able to add a survey.
We can also have the information,
edit information directly.
So, for now, none of the
questionnaire survey was not affected.
So here I come back to affect
the questionnaires, so for example I
select them all.
There you go, if I come back
here, I'm going to have access to all the
questionnaires. On the other hand, if I decide
for example, to affect only
Team Fonctioning and Safety
at work,
I will be able to select that
Team Fonctioning and Safety
at work on the investigation manager's side.
For example, I do Safety at Work.
So I don't really know maybe
what is Workplace Safety. I have here on
the question Mark, an overview of the
questionnaire in PDF format with
about fifteen questions on the
formalism yes, absolutely, rather yes,
rather no, no, not at all and without
opinion/ not concerned.
So I select the security at the
work and I will be able to inform the
information: name,
the period, the start date, the date of
end, the hour of end, what will go to me
provide access to results as soon as possible
that the schedule will be reached, a
final comment that I will be able to
customize and scope,
that is, the number of people who
will be asked to respond to
the investigation. This number allows
primarily to calculate a rate of
participation in the survey.
Test survey,
start date, and it will
end for example on the 30th at
noon, we can thank you
to the investigation
and for example 30 people. Therefore,
we see that it appears here. We will
be able to send emails from
solicitation or generating letters
with printable codes for employees
who would not have a professional
address. Then
here, you can have the follow-up at any time
of the answers. Well there, of course, none
has not yet been
connected to the survey and you can edit
at any time the information. So we
can change that the end date, time
and the perimeter. If the date of
was wrong, we delete
the investigation and we come back. The end date,
we will eventually be able to bring forward the
end date to get the report
early for example, what we're going to do just
after. We will also be able to delete the
the survey. Then Generate codes.
It will be with QR codes. We see that
mail is customizable. So we
see the logo we had selected
in Settings previously.
You can edit the text before and after.
We find the Pragma signature. In fact,
we're going to flash this QR code where we're going to go
directly on the address that will be
here when we receive the email and
we're going to fill in the code and we'll be able to
access the survey. We can generate a
code, you can generate several.
One can be generated. So now I'm going to
receive an email here.
Here you have your codes been generated [...] .
The questionnaire will be self-personalized
with the logo and the
green color that I had defined.
Next. So there, we can fill
the questionnaire.
And there, I find myself with the category
question that I have defined. I had
defined a city category, so
either Lyon or Paris.
And now, I find myself with the message that
I had modified with 'to the investigation' mention.
And there, I have an updated follow-up
with one employee, i.e. 3.3% per
compared to the 30 people I am expecting.
So there is the notion of exploitable here,
is that we have responded to at least 30% of the
questionnaire. We can send
emails, so there the same it's going to be
customizable. We will be able to copy the
emails. So, for example, if
I create another email address,
then random,
New
that I put this [...].
I completed the investigation and
closed by bringing forward the end date and
I created another survey to be able to
have a comparative report. So the
general report, it's going to be the entirety
of the answers, the report by categories.
In fact, we will be able to select the
city (e.g. Lyon)
and the comparative report for the same
template, so the same type of survey,
that is to say, Safety at work. We will
to be able to compare with the second,
on the left the selected survey, on the right
comparative survey.
We can disconnect.